const QUESTION=[
    {
      question:"Hyper Text Markup Language Stand For ?",
      options:["JavaScript", "XHTML","CSS", "HTML"],
      answer:"HTML",
    },
    {
      question:"Which language is used for styling web pages ?",
      options:["CSS", "JQuery", "CSS", "XML"],
      answer:"CSS",
    },
    {
      question:"Which is not a JavaScript Framework ?",
      options: ["Python Script", "JQuery","Django", "NodeJS"],
    answer:"Django",
  },
  {
    question:"Which is used for Connect To Database ?",
    options:["PHP", "HTML", "JS", "All"],
    answer:"PHP",
  },
  {
    question:"Saylani Mass IT training is about..",
    options:["Web Design", "Graphic Design", "SEO & Development", "All"],
    answer:"All"
  },
  {
    question:" Hypertext Preprocessor ?",
    options:["XML","PHP","HTP","JQuery"],
    answer:"PHP",
  },
  {
    question:"Hyper Text Markup Language Stand For ?",
    options:["JavaScript", "XHTML","CSS", "HTML"],
    answer:"HTML",
  },
  {
    question:"Which language is used for styling web pages ?",
    options:["CSS", "JQuery", "CSS", "XML"],
    answer:"CSS",
  },
  {
    question:"Which is not a JavaScript Framework ?",
    options: ["Python Script", "JQuery","Django", "NodeJS"],
  answer:"Django",
},
{
  question:"Which is used for Connect To Database ?",
  options:["PHP", "HTML", "JS", "All"],
  answer:"PHP",
},
{
  question:"Saylani Mass IT training is about..",
  options:["Web Design", "Graphic Design", "SEO & Development", "All"],
  answer:"All"
},
{
  question:" Hypertext Preprocessor ?",
  options:["XML","PHP","HTP","JQuery"],
  answer:"PHP",
},
]
const reducer=()=> QUESTION
export default reducer